- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
All:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
All:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute playing]
[长笛演奏]
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[jaunty music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh happy birthday on you ♪
- ♪ 哦，祝你生日快乐 ♪
♪ It's your birthday,
it's true ♪
♪ 这是你的生日，
这是真的♪
♪ It's the day
that I built you ♪
♪ 这一天
我创造了你♪
♪ Happy birthday on ♪
♪ 生日快乐 ♪
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Oh, Sheldon.
- 哦，谢尔顿。
This has been the best
birthday I've ever had.
这已经是最好的了
我曾经过的生日。
- And it ain't over yet.
- 事情还没有结束。
It's time for the birthday
girl to open her presents.
又到了生日的时间了
女孩打开她的礼物。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Ta-da.
哒哒。
- Oh?
- 哦？
- It's a gift certificate
for tango lessons.
- 这是一张礼券
探戈课。
- Oh, you know I'd love
to dance with you, sweetie,
- 哦，你知道我会喜欢
和你一起跳舞，亲爱的，
but we've tried this before.
但我们之前已经尝试过。
And if you recall...
如果你还记得...
- Yeah?
- 是的？
Oh, yeah?
哦，是吗？
Yee-haw.
呀呀。
[whistle tooting]
[吹口哨]
- It did not go well.
- 进展并不顺利。
- This time is going
to be different.
- 这一次即将过去
变得不同。
Because your other
birthday present is this.
因为你的另一个
生日礼物是这个。
The Leg Yanker Five Zillion.
腿扬克五亿。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
This is for you, baby.
这是给你的，宝贝。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Hmm, nice weather up here.
- 嗯，这里天气很好。
Whoa.
哇哦。
- Well, hello, tall,
green, and evil.
- 嗯，你好，高个子，
绿色，邪恶。
- May I have this dance?
- 我可以跳一支舞吗？
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Love the new stems, Plankton.
- 喜欢新茎，浮游生物。
Whoa.
哇哦。
- It's 8:00 p.m. already.
- 现在是晚上 8:00已经。
Where's our dance instructor?
我们的舞蹈老师在哪里？
- Hello, class.
- 你好，同学们。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- I'm your tango
instructor, Susie Groove.
- 我是你的探戈
教练，苏西·格鲁夫。
And when I'm done with you,
this is how you gotta move.
当我和你结束后
这就是你必须采取的行动方式。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
So everyone start dancing,
and I'll come
于是大家开始跳舞，
我会来
around and give you some tips.
周围并给你一些提示。
- ♪ Ahh ahh ahh,
la la la la la la la la ♪
- ♪ 啊啊啊啊，
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦♪
- You're breaking
the first rule, honey.
- 你打破了
第一条规则，亲爱的。
It takes two to tango.
探戈需要两个人。
- Sorry, Miss Groove.
- 对不起，格鲁夫小姐。
Mr. Krabs ordered me to be
Pearl's tango partner tonight,
蟹老板命令我
今晚珍珠的探戈舞伴，
but she just doesn't
dig my tangy moves.
但她就是不
挖掘我的刺激动作。
- SpongeBob, you can't tango.
- 海绵宝宝，你不会探戈。
I need a real dance partner,
我需要一个真正的舞伴
not a cackling,
bow-legged goofball.
不是咯咯笑声，
弓腿傻瓜。
No offense.
无意冒犯。
- I took it as a compliment.
- 我把它当作一种恭维。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- I can teach anyone to tango.
- 我可以教任何人探戈。
All you gotta do is...
你所要做的就是...
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Wow, you can tango.
- 哇，你会探戈。
Thanks to Susie Groove.
感谢苏西·格鲁夫。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- That's too close to tango.
- 这太接近探戈了。
♪ ♪
- One, two, three.
- 一二三。
One, two, three.
一二三。
Relax, Sheldon.
放松点，谢尔顿。
- I'm trying,
my little whirling dervish,
- 我正在努力，
我的旋转小苦行僧，
but these legs
have minds of their own.
但这些腿
有自己的主见。
Not that way, you idiots.
不是这样的，你们这些白痴。
Damn you.
该死的你。
Hya!
哈！
- Compose yourself, darling.
- 冷静点，亲爱的。
We're in public.
我们在公共场合。
- I know.
- 我知道。
I just need something
to balance me.
我只是需要一些东西
来平衡我。
See?
看？
It works.
有用。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Wait, I got it.
等等，我明白了。
I got it.
我得到了它。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- Stop dancing!
- 别跳舞了！
- Ow.
- Sorry, Susie.
- 噢。
- 对不起，苏西。
- I just washed my legs, and
I can't do a thing with them.
- 我刚刚洗了腿，然后
我对他们无能为力。
- Legs ain't your
problem, honey.
- 腿不是你的
问题，亲爱的。
If you want to tango,
you got to learn
如果你想跳探戈，
你必须学习
to dance with your hips.
用你的臀部跳舞。
- With my lips?
- 用我的嘴唇？
This isn't working.
这不起作用。
- Ugh.
- 呃。
- That's because I said hips.
- 那是因为我说的是臀部。
Watch me.
看着我。
All you got to do is...
你所要做的就是...
[percussive music]
[打击乐]
♪ ♪
- Wow, your hips are so hip.
- 哇，你的臀部太时髦了。
You got your work
cut out for you, Sheldon.
你得到了你的工作
谢尔顿，适合你。
- My hips can't do that.
- 我的臀部做不到这一点。
- Of course they can.
- 他们当然可以。
You got to force them to do it.
你必须强迫他们这样做。
The tango is physical,
emotional,
探戈是身体性的，
情绪化,
and most importantly,
aggressive.
最重要的是，
具有侵略性。
- What?
- 什么？
Aggressive?
挑衅的？
Now you're talking my language.
现在你正在说我的语言。
- Yeah,
we speak fluent aggression.
- 是的，
我们说着流利的攻击性语言。
- Good.
- 好的。
Tap into that aggression
and put it in your hips.
利用这种攻击性
并把它放在你的臀部。
Now, abrazo.
现在，阿布拉索。
Embrace.
拥抱。
Both: Abrazo.
两人：阿布拉索。
- Ready?
- 准备好？
All you gotta do is...
你所要做的就是...
- Terrific tangoing, Planktons.
- 很棒的探戈，浮游生物。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
I thought we were good.
我以为我们很好。
- Oh, how nice of you to say.
- 哦，你说得真好。
[yells]
[喊叫]
- Abrazo, my stinky cheese.
- 阿布拉索，我的臭奶酪。
- Abrazo, my rotten rose.
- 阿布拉索，我的烂玫瑰。
- Oh, no, I accidentally
dropped my spike strip.
-哦，不，我不小心
我的钉条掉了。
Oopsie.
哎呀。
- [yells]
- [大喊]
[piano trill]
[钢琴颤音]
[piano music]
[钢琴音乐]
[both chuckling]
[两人都笑了]
- We're the king
and queen of tango.
- 我们是国王
和探戈女王。
- OK, Planktons, take four.
- 好吧，浮游生物，拿四个。
Ahh!
啊！
- That wasn't very nice
of Plankton and Karen.
- 那不太好
浮游生物和凯伦。
- No, it wasn't,
but that's the tango, honey.
- 不，不是的，
但这就是探戈，亲爱的。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Bravo, Planktons.
- 太棒了，浮游生物。
Nice aggression.
很好的侵略性。
- Oh, thank you, Susie.
-哦，谢谢你，苏西。
I haven't had this much fun
since I got defragged.
我还没玩过这么多乐趣
自从我整理碎片后。
- I'd say we're the best
in the class, wouldn't you,
- 我想说我们是最好的
在课堂上，你不是吗
Miss Groove?
格鲁夫小姐？
- I think you're both great,
but my top students
- 我认为你们都很棒
但我的尖子生
might disagree.
可能不同意。
Both: Top students?
两人：尖子生？
- Yeah.
- 是的。
They're late today.
他们今天迟到了。
- The tango masters
have arrived.
- 探戈大师
已经到了。
- Sorry we're late.
- 抱歉我们迟到了。
Bubble Bass needed
clean underwear.
需要泡泡鲈鱼
干净的内衣。
- Mother.
- 母亲。
- Bubble Bass and his mom?
- 泡泡巴斯和他的妈妈？
- That's right.
- 这是正确的。
Mother and I have won the
Undersea Tango Championship
我和妈妈赢得了
海底探戈锦标赛
three years in a row.
连续三年。
We're the best.
我们是最好的。
- But yet somehow, and without
warning, we're the best!
- 但不知何故，而且没有
警告，我们是最棒的！
- I smell a dance-off.
- 我闻到了跳舞的味道。
- Insects first.
- 首先是昆虫。
Hmph.
哼。
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
Ta-da.
哒哒。
Well, try and out-tango that.
好吧，尝试跳探戈吧。
- Don't mind if we do.
- 如果我们这样做的话，不要介意。
♪ ♪
- Huh?
- 啊？
[both growling]
[双方咆哮]
- I said we're the best.
- 我说过我们是最好的。
Abrazo.
阿布拉索。
- Looks like someone
ordered a Bass sandwich.
- 看起来像某人
点了一份巴斯三明治。
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
- Well, that was fun.
- 嗯，那很有趣。
But I guess we're
not aggressive enough
但我想我们是
不够激进
to be the best.
成为最好的。
- Nobody is more
aggressive than us.
- 没有人比他更
比我们侵略性。
They just have more practice.
他们只是有更多的练习。
If only there was some way
we could cheat and show them
如果有什么办法就好了
我们可以欺骗并向他们展示
who's really the best.
谁才是真正最好的。
- Let's just go home, Sheldon.
- 我们回家吧，谢尔顿。
Here,
this fell out of your pocket.
在这里，
这是从你口袋里掉出来的。
- Ooh, it's my Ray-Ray ray,
the device
- 哦，这是我的射线，射线，
该设备
that turns me into my alter
ego with great hair, Ray-Ray.
这让我变成了我的分身
拥有漂亮头发的自我，雷雷。
That'll make me more aggressive.
这会让我变得更有攻击性。
- Ooh, you're right, Plankton.
- 哦，你说得对，浮游生物。
My Ray-Ray is the only one
who could take charge of this.
我的雷雷是唯一的
谁能负责这件事。
Hold still.
保持不动。
- It's Ray-Ray, baby.
- 这是雷雷，宝贝。
- Oops.
- 哎呀。
Sorry, wrong old man.
对不起，老哥，看错了。
- It's Ray-Ray, baby.
- 这是雷雷，宝贝。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Looks like someone ordered
a cold plate of revenge.
- 看起来有人订购了
复仇的冷盘。
- With extra humiliation.
- 带着额外的羞辱。
[both hissing]
[两人都发出嘶嘶声]
- Tango rematch, honey.
- 探戈复赛，亲爱的。
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- No.
- 不。
- Whoo!
- 呼！
- Whoa!
[laughs]
- 哇！
[笑]
Whoo!
呼！
Go, Ray-Ray, go.
走吧，雷雷，走吧。
- I want to hate the
Planktons, but they're so good.
- 我想讨厌
浮游生物，但它们太棒了。
- Oh, there, there, there.
- 哦，那里，那里，那里。
- He dances like an angel.
- 他跳舞得像个天使。
- Of death.
- 死亡。
- By the tango vested in me,
I pronounce Karen and Ray-Ray
- 以我赋予的探戈，
我发音为Karen 和Ray-Ray
my top students, honey.
我的尖子生，亲爱的。
- We did it, Ray-Ray.
- 我们做到了，雷雷。
We're the best.
我们是最好的。
- Happy birthday,
Karen-cakes, top of the world.
- 生日快乐，
凯伦蛋糕，世界之巅。
Now for the big finish.
现在是大结局。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Too much friction.
摩擦力太大。
Oh my...
哦天哪...
- My legs!
- 我的腿！
Sorry, that's my line.
抱歉，这是我的台词。
- Here, Plankton,
you can borrow my legs.
- 在这里，浮游生物，
你可以借用我的腿。
- No, thanks.
- 不，谢谢。
Mine are growing back already.
我的已经长回来了。
Thank you, Karen.
谢谢你，凯伦。
- It takes two to tango.
- 探戈需要两个人。
Come here, Ray-Ray.
过来，雷雷。
All: The name's Ray-Ray, baby.
全体：宝贝，我的名字叫雷雷。
Both: Uh-oh.
两人：呃哦。
[light bouncy music]
[轻快活泼的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Huh?
- [panting]
- 啊？
- [气喘吁吁]
Hmm?
唔？
- Mmm.
- 嗯。
- [munching]
- [咀嚼]
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
I just love breakfast.
我就是喜欢早餐。
- I don't mind overpaying
if it's breakfast.
- 我不介意多付钱
如果是早餐的话。
- Ooh, that money looks tasty.
- 哦，那钱看起来很好吃。
- Do you mind?
- 你介意吗？
- Sorry.
- 对不起。
All these people eating
breakfast is making me hungry.
这些人都在吃饭
早餐让我饿了。
Hungry for more customers
that is.
渴望更多客户
也就是说。
- Speaking of customers,
stop bothering mine.
- 说到客户，
别再打扰我的了。
- Ahh!
- 啊！
- Well,
that sure kick-started my day.
- 嗯，
这确实开启了我的一天。
- Morning, Mr. Krabs.
- 早上好，蟹老板。
- Good morning, Krusty crew.
- 早上好，Krusty 船员。
I have a fantastic
idea for me restaurant.
我有一个很棒的
我的想法餐厅。
- We're opening
a Krusty Krab on the moon?
- 我们要开业了
月球上的蟹堡王？
- We're closing down forever?
- 我们要永远关门了？
[loud explosion]
[爆炸声]
- What? No.
- 什么？不。
From now on, the Krusty Krab
will start serving breakfast.
从现在开始，蟹堡王
将开始供应早餐。
And you two get to come
to work even earlier.
你们两个一定要来
甚至更早去上班。
- Hmm?
- 唔？
- Oh, boy, I get to make
Krabby Patties for breakfast.
- 哦，孩子，我要做
早餐吃蟹肉饼。
- No, no, no, no, no.
- 不，不，不，不，不。
People don't want
patties in the morning.
人们不想要
早上吃肉饼。
They want bacon
and eggs and hash browns.
他们想要培根
还有鸡蛋和薯饼。
You know, breakfast stuff.
你知道，早餐的东西。
See if you can whip up
a stack of pancakes, boy-o.
看看你能不能振作起来
一堆煎饼，男孩。
- Yes, sir.
- 是的，先生。
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[bell dings]
[铃声]
- Give it the old mouth test,
Mr. Squidward.
- 进行旧口测试，
章鱼哥先生。
- These pancakes taste
like a Krabby Patty.
- 这些煎饼的味道
就像蟹肉饼一样。
- Oh.
- 哦。
I guess I only know how
to cook Krabby Patties.
我想我只知道如何
煮蟹黄饼。
- Oh, I was afraid of this.
- 哦，我很害怕这个。
Go down to the bookstore
and pick up the breakfast
下楼去书店
并拿起早餐
cookbook I ordered.
我订购的食谱。
You need to expand your
repertoire a bit, boy-o.
你需要扩展你的
有点曲目，男孩。
- Hello, I'm here to pick
up a cookbook for Mr. Krabs.
- 你好，我是来挑选的
为蟹老板准备一本食谱。
- Well, of course, sir.
- 嗯，当然，先生。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
Here you go.
干得好。
- Are you sure
this is the right book?
- 你确定吗
这是正确的书吗？
- Looks right to me.
- 对我来说看起来不错。
- Whoops, pardon me.
- 哎呀，请原谅我。
- What a polite
little hunk of cheese.
- 多么有礼貌啊
小块奶酪。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
I have a book on hold, last
name Witch, first name Evil.
我有一本书搁置，最后
名字女巫，名字邪恶。
- Certainly.
- 当然。
Must be this one.
一定是这个。
Your book, ma'am.
你的书，女士。
- I forgot my spectacles.
- 我忘记戴眼镜了。
Hey, buddy, you sure this
is the magic book I ordered?
嘿，伙计，你确定这个
是我订购的魔法书吗？
- Pretty sure.
- 很确定。
- Huh?
- 啊？
If you say so.
如果你这么说的话。
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
[all grumbling]
[大家都在抱怨]
- I got the cookbook,
Mr. Krabs.
- 我拿到了食谱，
蟹老板。
- Hurry up, boy-o.
- 快点，男孩。
Breakfast don't last
all day, you know.
早餐不持久
一整天，你知道。
- Love potions, summoning
demons, the undead and you.
- 爱情魔药，召唤
恶魔、亡灵和你。
Oh, breakfast.
哦，早餐。
"Stacks of woe."
“成堆的祸患。”
That must mean pancakes.
那一定是指煎饼。
This book sure calls
for some weird ingredients.
这本书确实呼吁
一些奇怪的成分。
Mr. Krabs, do we have
any zombie teeth,
蟹老板，我们有吗？
任何僵尸牙齿，
dragon's breath, eye of newt?
龙息，蝾螈之眼？
- Well, there should be some
in the back of the freezer.
- 嗯，应该有一些
在冰箱的后面。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
- What?
- 什么？
I can't pass up a sale.
我不能错过促销。
- Found them.
- 找到他们了。
Must be cooked
in an iron cauldron.
一定要煮熟
在铁锅里。
Ooh, classy.
哦，优雅。
I think there's one
in here somewhere.
我认为有一个
在这里的某个地方。
Oh, there you are.
哦，你来了。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[muffled scream]
[低沉的尖叫声]
- Oh, they're glorious.
- 哦，他们很光荣。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Looks tasty.
看起来很好吃。
Mr. Squidward, you're up again.
章鱼哥先生，你又起来了。
- Say, these are pretty good.
- 说吧，这些都很好。
Breakfast is served.
供应早餐。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Your oatmeal, sir.
- 你的燕麦片，先生。
- Mmm.
- 嗯。
Deliciously bland.
味道清淡可口。
- I woke up
before noon for this?
- 我醒了
中午之前就为了这个？
Where is my morning sustenance?
我早上的食物在哪里？
- Your waffles.
- 你的华夫饼。
- A meal most toothsome.
- 一顿最美味的饭菜。
Time to pay for my repast.
是时候付我的饭钱了。
Ow.
噢。
Egad, my hindquarters
have gone rogue.
埃加德，我的后躯
已经变得无赖了。
- I am beyond offended.
- 我非常生气。
- [howls]
- [嚎叫]
- [hisses]
- [嘶嘶声]
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇，
哇，哇，哇。
- Who ordered the parfait?
- 谁点了冻糕？
[all shouting, howling]
[大家大喊大叫，嚎叫]
- Huh? Huh? Huh?
- 啊？啊？啊？
Of course.
当然。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 哇，哇，哇，哇。
- SpongeBob.
- 海绵宝宝。
What the ham and eggs
is going on around here?
火腿和鸡蛋是什么
这附近有什么事吗？
- Oh, I don't think I've got
the hang of this breakfast
- 哦，我想我没有
这顿早餐的窍门
thing, Mr. Krabs.
事情，蟹老板。
- [chattering]
- [喋喋不休]
- A cup of milk?
- 一杯牛奶？
Two eggs?
两个鸡蛋？
A loaf of bread?
一条面包？
And kelp sugar?
还有海带糖？
Eh, all right.
呃，好吧。
Shoo.
嘘。
French toast?
法式吐司？
Hash browns?
薯饼？
Quiche?
乳蛋饼？
Huevos rancheros?
休沃斯牧场主？
What the heck?
到底是什么？
What's wrong with this
blasted spell book?
这是怎么回事
该死的咒语书？
"Uncle Jimmy's Breakfast Magic"?
《吉米叔叔的早餐魔法》？
It's a cookbook.
这是一本食谱。
Oh.
哦。
I better find out who got
my spell book, and fast.
我最好找出谁得到了
我的咒语书，而且速度很快。
Huh?
啊？
Right after I finish my quiche.
就在我吃完乳蛋饼之后。
- Why is this happening?
- 为什么会发生这种情况？
- Maybe all the weird
stuff I've been cooking
- 也许一切都很奇怪
我一直在煮的东西
caused all of this.
造成了这一切。
[chuckling]
[轻笑]
Would explain the cauldron too.
也会解释一下锅。
And the flying cookbook.
还有飞行食谱。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
♪ ♪
The cookbook
is using tasty breakfast
食谱
正在使用美味的早餐
treats to create a monster.
治疗来创造一个怪物。
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Oh, so this is where
my spell book went.
- 哦，这就是地方
我的咒语书不见了。
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
- Ooh, a customer.
- 哦，一位顾客。
Take her order, Squidward.
听她的命令，章鱼哥。
- Uh, thanks, but I
couldn't eat another bite.
- 呃，谢谢，但是我
不能再吃一口了。
[belches]
[打嗝]
I'm here to swap books with you.
我是来和你交换书籍的。
I think my spell book got
mixed up with your cookbook.
我想我的咒语书得到了
和你的食谱混在一起了。
But first, I better take
care of this foodie fiasco.
但首先，我最好采取
照顾这个美食家的惨败。
Flippity floppity food.
软软的食物。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
[babbling]
[胡说]
Ah!
Not maple syrup.
啊!
不是枫糖浆。
I'm sticky.
我很粘。
So sticky.
太粘了。
Hey, you, the spongy kid
with the wand.
嘿，你这个海绵宝宝
用魔杖。
- That's a spatula.
- 那是一把抹刀。
- My wand.
- 我的魔杖。
- Well, I'll lend you
some of my magic.
- 好吧，我借给你
我的一些魔法。
The only way to stop breakfast
is with its mortal enemy...
停止吃早餐的唯一方法
与它的死敌……
dinner.
晚餐。
- Oh, I can do dinner.
- 哦，我可以做晚饭。
Pippity poppity pot roast.
皮皮蒂罂粟炖肉。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
[all yelling]
[大家大喊]
- No.
- 不。
Squidward is not part
of a balanced breakfast,
章鱼哥不是一部分
均衡的早餐，
a triple-decker Krabby Patty.
三层甲板的克拉比帕蒂
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
- With cheese.
- 配奶酪。
Wah!
哇！
- Mmm.
- 嗯。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[loud explosion]
[爆炸声]
Ahh!
啊！
Oh!
哦！
[groaning]
[呻吟]
I need a vacation.
我需要一个假期。
- Hey, kid, do you want
to be my apprentice?
- 嘿，孩子，你想要吗？
做我的徒弟？
You got a real knack for magic.
你确实有魔法天赋。
- Thanks.
- 谢谢。
But the only magic
I need is the delicious
但唯一的魔力
我需要的是美味
taste of a Krabby Patty.
蟹肉饼的味道。
- Eh.
- 呃。
A patty?
一块肉饼？
It's a little early for me.
对我来说有点早了。
Unless...
除非...
Hmm.
唔。
A Krabby waffle.
蟹黄华夫饼。
- Ooh, a Krabby waffle, eh?
- 哦，蟹黄华夫饼，嗯？
I have another brilliant idea.
我还有另一个好主意。
We will no longer
be serving breakfast.
我们将不再
正在供应早餐。
From now on, the Krusty Krab
will be serving "brinner."
从现在开始，蟹堡王
将提供“brinner”。
- Ooh, the breakfast-dinner duo.
- 哦，早餐晚餐二人组。
- And this time, I picked
up the new cookbook myself.
- 而这一次，我选择了
我自己写了新的食谱。
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
[ghosts howling]
[鬼魂嚎叫]
Hey, we've got customers.
嘿，我们有顾客了。